Mustafa Madkour

Web Developer

PERSONAL INFORMATION

mustafamdkr@gmail.com

Alexandria, Egypt (Egypt)

02 July 1990

💯 Male

🗀 Egyptian

/ +201280918403

+201011255930

https://www.github.com/MustafaMDKR

in mustafa-madkour-dev

MOTHER TONGUE(S)

Arabic

FOREIGN LANGUAGE(S)

English

Listening: C1 Reading: C1 Spoken interaction: C1

Writing: B2

SUMMARY

Career shifter web developer who has many diffirent backgrounds and enjoy coding and learning new technologies. Self taught web development in mern stack and has little experience in python web development.

Check my guthub account for projects

AREAS OF EXPERTISE



WORK EXPERIENCE

Accountant

15 January 2012 - 31 May 2015

Astron Manufacturing & Engineering | Alexandria

Posting and processing journal entries to ensure all business transactions are recorded Updating accounts receivable and issue invoices Updating accounts payable and perform reconciliations

Business or sector: Head Office

Accountant 01 June 2015 - 31 May 2019

AlexTech Marine Services | Alexndria

Posting and processing journal entries to ensure all business transactions are recorded Updating accounts receivable and issue invoices Updating accounts payable and perform reconciliations

Developer 01 June 2019 - Present

AlexTech Marine Services | Alexandria

Develop business solutions to solve urgent problems
Design & implement embedded systems based in Microcontrollers
Excute Electrical projects & Diagrams

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Accountancy

22 September 2007 - 08 June 2011

Alexandria University | Alexandria